(Leonard:)Happened to Einstein. He got stuck
in the unified field theory for decades.
(Sheldon:)Oh, don't play the Einstein card.
His breakthroughs happened
when no one knew anything.
(Sheldon:)Everything was a great breakthrough.
(Leonard:)Sheldon Lee Cooper,
I do not have time for this nonsense.
(Leonard:)Go put your clothes on,
get in the car, and let's go to work.
All right, jeez.
(Sheldon:)What a grouch.
(Leonard:)How did I do that?
I gotta remember how I did that.
(Howard:)Do you realize by owning a 3D printer...
(Howard:)...we are reclaiming
the manufacturing process...
(Howard:)...and taking jobs back
from sweatshops in China.
(Raj:)I think this thing was made in China.
(Howard:)Eh, what can you do?
Ooh, I think it's done.
(Raj:)It worked.
(Raj:)We printed a whistle.
(Howard:)Amazing.
(Howard:)You realize these things go
for 25 cents a pop at a party store.